Guide to the Stanford University Newspaper Clippings
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Clippings, Accession ARCH-1995-075
  - Subject clippings out of alpha order:
    - Centrifuge (developed at Stanford; see also Beckman Instruments or Medical Equipment) (Box 8)
    - Charter Medical Corp. (Box 8)
    - Children's Center at Stanford (Box 8)
    - Children's Hospital Retirement Home (Box 8)
    - Churchill Street Jazz Band (Box 8)
    - Committee for Art at Stanford (Box 8)
    - Coretech (Council on Research and Technology) (Box 8)
    - Copus Inc. (Box 8)
    - Daily Californian (Box 8)
    - Danforth Foundation (Box 8)
    - Francesco Trio (Box 8)
    - Frank, Rimmerman & Co. (Box 8)
    - Free Campus Movement (Box 8)
    - French (Language) (Box 8)
    - Frenchman's Hill (Box 8)
    - Friends of Dance at Stanford (Box 8)
    - Friends of the Free Campus Movement (Box 8)
    - Frost Amphitheater (Box 8)
    - Games 'n Things (Box 8)
    - Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford (GLAS) (Box 8)
    - Gekee Fiberoptics (Box 8)
    - Governor Stanford (CA's 1st steam locomotive) (Box 8)
    - G-CSF (granulocyte colony stimulating factor) (Box 8)
    - Hanna-Honeycomb House - Stanford University (Box 8)
    - Hill-Burton Act (Box 8)
    - Hillel Foundation (Box 8)
    - Historic House Association of America (HHAA) (Box 8)
    - Institute of International Education (Box 8)
    - Institute for Molecular Biology (Box 8)
    - Institute for Philosophical Research (Box 8)
    - Institute for the Study of Human Knowledge (Box 8)
    - InveXtek (Box 8)
    - Irvine, James Foundation (Box 8)
    - Jet Lagg (Box 8)
    - Johnson & Company Jewelers (Box 8)
    - Knoll, The (Box 8)
    - Magna Carta (Box 8)
    - Marguerite Shuttle (Box 8)
    - McDonald House (Children's Hospital at Stanford) (Box 8)
    - Music Guild at Stanford (formerly Friends of Music) (Box 8)
    - Musick's Recreation (Box 8)
    - Mother's Club of Stanford University (Box 8)
    - Playground for the Performing Arts (see also: Actors' Playground (junior group)) (Box 8)
    - Radiation at Stanford (Box 8)
    - Reagan Library, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Reagan Library, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Serra House (Box 8)
    - Sheridan (Box 8)
    - Shreve & Co. (Box 8)
    - Shuttle Bus (Box 8)
    - Sisters-in-Stanford (Box 8)
    - Sterling Award (J.E. Wallace Sterling) (Box 8)
    - Stanford Music Hall (Box 8)
    - Stanford Outdoor Primate Facility (Box 8)
    - Stanford Repertory Theater (Box 8)
    - Stanford Research Institute (Box 8)
    - Stanford Research Institute, 1959, 1960, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Stanford Research Institute (SRI, incl. SRI International), 1976- (Box 8)
    - Stanford Research Institute - International Building (Box 8)
    - Stanford Solar Observatory (Box 8)
    - Stanford Solar Systems, Inc. (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, to 1960 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1961-1962 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1963 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1964 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1965 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1966 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1967 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1969 (see also: Stanford University Demonstrations and Dispute with the Stanford Research Institute) (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1970 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1971 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1972 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1976-1978 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University, 1978- (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Black Student Volunteer Center (Box 8)
    - Stanford University - Demonstrations and Dispute with Stanford Res. Inst. (Box 8)
    - Stanford University - Hoover Institute on War, Revolution and Peace (see Hoover Institute) (Box 8)
    - Stanford University History (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Hospital (formerly Palo Alto-Stanford Hospital; see also Stanford University Medical Center) (Box 8)
    - Stanford University - Instant Library (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Libraries (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Linear Accelerator, to 1965 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Linear Accelerator, 1966- (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Medical Center, to 1963 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Medical Center, 1964-1965 (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Medical Center 1966- (also see Stanford University Hospital) (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Microwave Lab (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Press (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Primate Facility (Box 8)
    - Stanford University Radar Telescope (Box 8)
    - Stanford University -Summer Festival of the Arts (Box 8)
    - Stanford University - Varian Laboratory of Physics (Box 8)
    - Stanford Village (see Dibble Hospital) (Box 8)
    - Thum Wrasslin (Box 8)
    - Tinker Foundation (New York) (Box 8)
    - Think Tanks (Box 8)
    - Tower Commission (see also: Iran Arms Scandal) (Box 8)
    - Transplants, through 1979 (Box 8)
    - Transplants, 1980-1982 (Box 8)
    - Transplants, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Transplants, 1984-1986 (Box 8)
    - Transplants, 1987-1989 (Box 8)
    - Transplants, 1990- (see also: organs, heart transplants, heart-lung transplants, kidneys, lungs) (Box 8)
    - Vallejo (see also: Stanford Studies) (Box 8)